Evil Awaits.
Wrong Turn 2: Dead End is a horror, thriller film directed by Joe Lynch.
Retired military commander Colonel Dale Murphy hosts the simulated post-apocalyptic reality show
where participants are challenged to survive a remote West Virginia wasteland.
But the show turns into a nightmarish showdown when each realizes they are being hunted
by an inbred family of cannibals determined to make them all dinner!
Nina Papas, played by Erica Leerhsen.
Dale Murphy, played by Henry Rollins.
Jake Washington, played by Texas Battle.
Mara, played by Aleksa Palladino.
Amber, played by Daniella Alonso.
Jonesy, played by Steve Braun.
Wrong Turn 2: Dead End is a 2007 slasher film directed by Joe
Lynch and written by Turi Meyer and Al Septien.
An international co-production between Summit Entertainment from the United States and Constantin Film from
Germany, it is a sequel to Wrong Turn (2003) and the second installment in the Wrong Turn film series.
Starring Erica Leerhsen, Henry Rollins, Texas Battle, Aleksa Palladino, Daniella Alonso, Steve Braun, Crystal Lowe, Matthew Currie Holmes and Kimberly Caldwell, and follows
a group of reality show contestants fighting for their survival against a family of horribly deformed cannibals who plan to mercilessly slaughter them all.
Wrong Turn 2: Dead End had its premiere at the FrightFest on August 25, 2007, and was released on
DVD in the United States on October 9, 2007, by 20th Century Fox Home Entertainment.
The film received a positive response from critics, which
remains the best-reviewed film in the franchise.
It grossed $9.2 million in home video sales.
It is followed by Wrong Turn 3: Left for Dead (2009).
The film explores themes of competition,
dynamite, forest, west virginia, sequel.
The tone is dark and intense.